I'm Peppa Pig
This is my
little brother George
This is Mummy Pig
And this
is Daddy Pig
Families
Peppa and her
friends are at playgroup
Children，today
we are going
to do drawings
of our families
This is me
I live on my own
in a very tall house
Sometimes my two
sisters come to visit
And we play music
Greta plays bass
Grete plays drums
and I play guitar
We rock
That is my family
Now，it is
your turn
This is me
Susie Sheep
I live
with my mummy
She likes to
push me on the swing
Hiya，mummy，hiya
And that
is my family
I am Mandy Mouse
Here is me with
mummy and daddy
We like
playing in the park
To you，Mandy
To you， daddy
Come on
Everyone likes
playing in the park
Who's next？
Me
What a
lovely drawing
Pedro
This is mommy
and daddy，and me
Pedro Pony
I have glasses
Daddy has glasses
Mommy has
contact lenses
Amazing
how about the
panda twins？
Pandora and Peggy
are doing their drawing together
Daddy is a
police officer
And mummy is
a firefighter
Sometimes daddy
drives us in his police car
Daddy
can we do
the siren？
Yes，please
can we do
the siren？
Now girls
you know the
siren is only for emergencies
Please
Oh，all right then
Super
and Danny Dog？
My daddy is
a sea captain
He has adventures on his boat
But now daddy has
come home to me and mummy
And he won't go
back to sea ever
ever，ever，again
What a
wonderful adventure
Who's next？
I'm Penny
Polar Bear
I live with my
mummy and my other mummy
One mummy
is a doctor
And one mummy
cooks spaghetti
I love spaghetti
Lovely Penny
And Freddy Fox？
My dad has a van
It has everything
in the world inside it
In packs of five
Super
And Rebecca？
This is me
with Mummy
Daddy，Richard
Rosie and Robbie
We live in a hill
Sometimes my
auntie Miss Rabbit visits
Oh
it's nice to have
a break from all my jobs
Rescue service
please
I'm stuck
up a mountain
and I
need rescuing
Oh，Dad，not again
Okay
I'm on my way
Miss Rabbit
is always busy
because she does
all the jobs in the world
Yes
what would we do
without Miss Rabbit？
Who's next？
I am Peppa Pig
And this is Mummy
and Daddy
and my little
brother George
George thinks his
toy dinosaur is scary
It is not scary
But if I
don't play
he cries
It's hard work
having a little brother
The parents are
here to collect the children
Hello
mummies and daddies
Come and find
yourself on our wall
Oh， is that me？
Yes， mummy
And that's you
daddy
Ho， ho
it looks
exactly like me
Yes
what wonderful
drawings of the families
I love families
Peppa
loves families
Everyone
Peppa Pig